Thank you for watching!
And now, it's time for our host, Bananaman of Nogizaka Construction Workshops, to welcome you to the show.
This is Bananaman, the host of Nogizaka Construction Workers' Ch...
Let's see if I can draw this well.
Oh!
Himura-san, please announce what we're going to do today.
Let's go! Art Game Tournament 2023!
All right, all right!
This time, we'll form a team led by a member who is good at drawing.
We're going to play a game using drawing.
This is team Kaki!
Kaki is good!
Sakaguchi is good, too.
Shall we draw a picture of the other world?
It's funny, isn't it?
Nakamura toga, are you good?
Yes, he is
He's not very good.
I'm told he's not very good.
What do you mean, "bad at it"?
Next, team Inoue
Inoue's good.
I can't imagine Shibata.
It says "Shibata, unskilled.
What the hell?
And Team Ikeda.
Please.
Ikeda's already great?
He got into Geidai.
He didn't.It's not in there.
I'm sorry, but it's true.
I'm sorry. It's a big deal.
Shibata got a T-shirt the other day.
It's true... idiots draw.
I can't talk about it again.
I'm not stupid.
You should tell them I'm not stupid.
I'm dense.
That was stupid.
The painting, you know.
How about Tsutsui or something?
Normal eyes.
It says Tsutsui's not very good.
That's a little rude.
Let's play the first game.
Mr. Himura, please.
Guess the name of the illustration.
Four representatives from each team will guess
to illustrate a part of the lyrics of a song from each of the Nogizaka stations
Each illustration represents a part of the lyrics of each song.
The rest of the team members guess the name of the song from the 4 illustrations
If the remaining members can guess the name of the song from the four illustrations, they get 10 points.
This is each team leader coming up.
Each team
For each team
Each team leader comes up
and each time is one minute.
You only have one minute.
A picture that leads to the title
And no obvious pictures of choreography.And no obvious pictures of choreography.
Absolutely nothing.
And no numbers.
If you write a number, it's the end of the line.
Of course, you can't do that if you're writing letters.
Of course.
Like "whoo hoo".
But people tend to do that.
I understand.
I'm sorry... about the rules.
I'm sorry.
Can you apologize a little?
I'm sorry, but we want you to have fun.
We have a rule.
You have one minute.
The four of you have one minute to draw a picture of any part of a lyric that's been cut out.
Can you include as many clues as possible
Can you include as many clues as possible?
First, check out the team Kakino picture
Let's start with Kakino!
Wow, that's good!
But it's so abstract.
But it's a Nogizaka song!
I wonder which song's lyrics Kakinoe wrote part of?
I hope this is a miracle!
Yay!
Let's go, Sato!
What?
You're kidding.You're lying.
Sounds like a trick.
I thought it was the waves, but then I hear you looking at the river.
That's amazing.
It's got "sweetbreads" written all over it.
It can't be "sweetbreads." He's good only with sweetbreads.
I don't understand it all at once.
I don't know, but it makes it sound like we're getting there.
I'm serious.
There's one floating around.
Don't tell me yet.
Oh, my God.
Oh, no.
No, the creek is definitely not floating.
Fate has come through for us.
Let's go downhill.
Let's make a change today.
Let's change it today.
Huh.
Uh...
It's probably the wrong eye.
It says "stick figure" on it.
What?
"Stick figure.
The artist.
I don't get it at all.
I can see why there's a star in the lower part of the picture
I can tell there's a star.
Yes, it looks like night.Yeah, it's nighttimey.
Nighty-nighty.
Okay, Sameer.
Sameer.
Here you go.
Ha!
Ah!
Hatena, this is a little subtle.
Only this time
This time it's okay.
Just this once.
What's this? Are you crying?
I can see you're crying.
Team Kaki, could you find the correct answer in these four pictures?
Please, let's do this.
Synchronicity
What do you think?
Yes!
That's great!
Where did you get this?
That's great.
They're different.
They're passing each other.
Ibijirajira people.
So you figured it out here.
Yes, sir.
You're a great team leader, aren't you?
But... you had a problem with Sakaguchi once.
You wondered what was going on, right?
I thought, "This must be filled with tears.
Is this a picture of tears overflowing?Is this a picture of tears welling up?
No, it's crying when you suddenly realize you're crying.
No, it's not.
What state would you be in if you suddenly found yourself...
Tears.
There are tears, and this is some kind of a monster's hand.
It's a hand.
A hand...
I suddenly found myself in tears.
Oh, I cried unexpectedly... are these all tears?
This is not us bananaman.
This is a waterless man.
This is a waterless man passing by.
Oh, it's true.
And I'm drawing heavenly colors.
Heavenly colors
What is that?
It's a body.
It's his body.
Where is it?
Please go to the American Idol sometime.
You can tell it's nighttime.
He's just walking around at night.
But this picture could have been pretty good.
Really...
Ise Shrine...
I can't think of any reason.
I'm crying.
This last one...
10 points for this.Well done 10 points!
Yay!
that's what I'm talking about
Thank you very much!
Next, check out the illustration of Team Inoue's lyrics!
How about the one of the enemy team? Did you recognize it?
I didn't get it!
That's right.
You need to be able to draw, but you also need to be able to read the other team's lyrics.
The ability to read.
Okay, team Inoue.
Zdobon!
Oh!
What's this?
You wrote a lot!
You wrote a lot
I don't know...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Please don't talk.
No, no, no...
But I think you're confusing this with a lot of other songs.
It's still not right.
I wrote a lot.
Let's go.
Yes, sir.
Boom!
Ha-ha-ha!
What?
I drew a creepy picture.I drew a sickening picture.
From where?
Where did it come from?
I don't know.
I have no idea.
Was there a song by Kikkaida?
There's a song about that.
Yes, there is.
We're in a big meeting.
We're having a big meeting.
There are still two more.
Yes, there are.
Four tones.
That's it.
Here we go.
But there are so many songs like this.
There you go.
Come on. Come on.
Even with this, if you don't balance the clues properly, you could still make a mistake.
You're right.
It doesn't match.
It's the same song.
Yes, it does.
Yes, we do.
Okay.
Let's go ahead and do it.
Here you go.Here you go.
It's a train again.
Train.
So...
That's not what it means.
That's not what I'm talking about.
That's not what it's about.
There are a lot of songs with trains in them, aren't there?
Heh.
What?
Let's go.
Have you got it all together?
I don't know.
I feel like I'm lost.
Why?
The song that we came up with from the four pictures of the confused team Inoue is
Seino
You scolded me
You scolded me, what do you think?
Wah!
Se-no
Because that's where the scolded train is coming from.
He was angry.
Mr. Genka's
He scolds you.
Wasn't there a few more?
I meant good-bye.
That's not right.
The train... is it here... or is it just a mess around here?
I'm in love... and I'm holding my arms out.
Arrows are no good.Arrows no good.
No.
So, I'm going back to the train with my arms outstretched, and I'm taking my first step.
First step.
First step is still the first step, isn't it?
This is before you take the first step.
First step.
Ah!
Is that a mannequin in uniform?
Oh!
Train train train train train
So I like trains too much.
I know it's a train for the state store.
But I'm still getting lost in the trains.
And then there's this... this creepy thing.
What is that?
It's in my head.
You want to answer it in your head?
It's hard... but I'm sure it applies to many things.
It's about falling in love and not letting hot guys and adults get in the way.
No, it's too hard.
There you go.
Is this the same thing?
I'll jump in with both hands at the same place.
Oh, my God.
Dive in both hands!
No points for team Inoue.
You scolded me, but it was on a train.
What are you doing?
It's hard, isn't it?
It's so frustrating!It's so frustrating.
It's so frustrating that I can't guess what it is.
It's so frustrating.
You almost got it, didn't you?
I guess you could tell.
What kind of illustration did Team Ikeda draw?
Yamashita seems to have some inspiration.
I wonder if it's possible.
Let him have it.
Let's go, Team Leader Ikeda!
Don!
Lots and lots of it!
Oh!
It's so good!
It's really good.
It's good.
But there are so many songs like this.
They're good.
Okay, let's move on.
Here we go!
Here they come!
This is so good!
I can't believe I gave you the same minute.
I saw this picture in kindergarten.
Right?
Here it is.
Here.
Boom!thud
Oops!
That's good.
That's easy to understand.
This is easy to understand
Let's go, let's go!
Here we go.
Oops.
It's the same picture... almost here.
They're very close.
Did Ikeda's team find the correct answer among the four pictures?
Seino...
I've got a crush on you!
What do you think?
We did it!
It's over.
It's already the first one.
Yes, we all knew it from the first picture.
Oh, my God.
We knew it was Christmas and Valentine's Day!
I'm so happy!
You're really good in that short time, aren't you?
Yes...
I gave you the same minute.
Same minute.
But it's very easy to understand.
You like this one a lot, too, don't you?
Well, well, well, well, well, we got another team with a lot of hearts.
I'll take that as a yes.Let's say it's okay.
Isn't it great that you two are almost exactly the same?
You want to call him and hear his voice.
This phone is... well, it's old.
It's old.
It's a little difficult to use a smartphone.
It's beautiful.
Brilliant.
Two teams are already up 10 points each, so this could be impossible to reverse.
Impossible in the first game.
Let's move on to the next game.
Don't cover the image illustration game
What's this?
All team members draw an illustration that reminds them of the theme at the same time.
Only the illustration that can be drawn without overlapping with other team members will be awarded points.
Time limit is 30 seconds.
Can you come up with something that doesn't overlap with anyone else in an instant?
First, Team Inoue challenged
The theme for Team Inoue was white food.
That's great!
Let's get started!
Can you draw a picture in 30 seconds that is easy to understand without being the same as the other members of the team?
Yes, we're done! Yes, Daniel-san!
Let's go! Here you go!
Jean!
Oh my God, I don't know what this is?
White food?
It's an albacore.
Albacore?
It's a bit squishy. It's more squishy than that.
It's okay.Well, that's okay, isn't it?
Don't albino all the weird pictures.
So it gets tougher from here.
Okay, let's go.
Boom!
Shellfish?
Shells, right?
Scallops.
Scallops don't mean this is in it.
They're chopsticks.
Open it and see if it's this.
If it's like this, why did they do it?
But...
So-so, but white is fine.
Albacore, scallop.
You don't get the first one.
All right, let's continue.
Ready, go!
Ah!
I know, I know, I know.
It's beef stew.
No, it's not beef stew.
Help me out here.
White.
Make it white.
I know.
White.
Cream stew.
Thank you.
Well, it's not that different.Well, I don't think so.
That's fine.
Here we go.
What's this?
I don't know.
It's got a kind of a springy feel to it.
So if it's not pulled, it's bread.
Because the bread is pulled.
Pulled.
No, it's not.
No, no, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
What do you mean?
What the hell is this?
Reverse it.
Inverted.
Inverted?
Inverted is okay.
Here we go.
Here you go.
Jan.
Oh, my God.
I knew you had it in you.
This is corporate rebellion.
Leave the food on the table.
Food.
Mochi.
Mochi is good.Rice cakes are nice.
Not bad at all.
It's good.
Oh.
That's a tongue hug.
No, it's not.
That's a penis.
Dumplings.
I was trying to make sense of it until the last minute.
It's got a certain feel to it.
But it's good.
It's fine.
Here they are.
Here you go!
Shinkansen window
Hey...
Don't eat.
What's this?
Is that a Hampen?
It's a marshmallow.
I don't understand.
Marshmallows.
Marshmallows?
Don't tell me now.
Here you go.
Milt!Albacore.
That's what happened.
Arnu and I were talking about albacore just the other day.
You know...
Why are you talking about albacore?
You're good at it. I love it.
So, Team Inoue got 6 points for the albacore!
What do you want to do, Yokin?
The theme for Team Ikeda was food that starts with "A".
Can you come up with a picture in 30 seconds that doesn't cover the same food?
Here we go!
Let's go!
Here's a food that starts with "a".
American Docks.
That's right.
How did you know?
I just had it.
It's okay... we don't have to share.
That's good.
You didn't get very far, did you?
I must've messed it up.
Here you go.
Don!
Ha-ha!
Ah!
Candy is not bad
I couldn't think of any.
Candy's not number one.
Maybe it's all candy from here.
Candy's not bad, I think.I don't think candy is a bad idea.
I didn't think of that.
Here we go.
Let's go!
What's this?
What is this?
what is this?
what's this?
This is the same thing, right?
It's the same thing.
Wasabi?
It's the first time
Is it that good?
Asparagus
Correct.
asparagus
Asparagus
It's good. It's good.
It's good.
Spend a little more time.
Okay.
That's close enough.
I think it's a pickle.
Yeah. - Yeah.
I think pickle.
Pickles.
I think I found it. I think I found it.
I ate it.
I didn't eat it.
I did it!There we go.
Let's go.
Here you go.
Asparagus.
- Wow! He's so strong! Strong! Strong! Strong!
And you're good at it.
If you cook asparagus, it's the best so far!
Let's cover the asparagus.
Let's cover it with asparagus!
Maybe we'll get asparagus.
Please, please, please.
No, no, no...
It's something like...
A drink.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Laughs.
That's true.
Drinks
Drinks are alcohol.
Alcohol.
What is this?
It's green juice.
Oh, green juice
No, not a drink.
No drinks.
Well, I can make something okay, but...
I'm getting an onslaught of people watching.
You're spoiling it.
That's right.
Now, we're in big trouble.Come on. We're in big trouble.
We're in big trouble.
We're in trouble.
We can't score.
Come on, let's go.
Here you go.
Oh, sour.
This is asparagus.
Oh, no, no, no, we have three asparagus.
No points from the first two.
Suddenly they're not coming in.
Oh, no.
I've got three asparagus and a lot of green juice.
Let's go.
Shall we go?
American knock-knock.
Asparagus heads.
Ice cream.
Ice cream is okay.
I thought there would be a lot of ice cream.
I thought we were going to have ice cream.
First it was ice cream.
I thought there was going to be ice cream, but when I got out, it was an American dog.
What kind of magic was that?
Ice cream.
How did you do that?
Come on, team leader!
Don't ever wear that!Don't ever wear that.
That's the face you're wearing, too.
Don't ever wear that.
Let's go.
Candy!
It's not candy.
That's why it's candy. - That's why it's candy.
It's candy.
I'm gonna go hard on this one.
Candy. Candy.
It's candy.
That means only ice cream and American dog.
Four points.
Four.
There was a sudden brake here.
More shocking food appeared later!
Team Kakie's theme was food starting with vinegar.
Were they able to mass produce pictures that don't overlap with any of the other members?
Now, do you have anything to share here, too?
Yes.
Then, let's go.
Yes, sir.
Vinegared buckwheat noodles?
No, sir.
What is this?
Vinegared soba?
No, sir.
It's vinegar, right?
Vinegar.Vinegar.
It was served at school lunch.
At lunch?
What? Did I get it wrong?
What is this?
Is it vinegar in the vinegar?
Isn't that vinegar in it?
You got it.
Is that vinegar in the vinegar?
Vinegar infused juice is kind of cute.
Is there something in it?
Vinegar.
No vinegar.
Oh, no!
I should've said yes to the soba noodles with vinegar.
I'm sure we'll never get the same thing.
That's funny.
It's funny... that's what this is all about.
It's a little late to be making these.
What? What's that?
It's vinegar.
It's covered with vinegar.
If it's vinegar in the vinegar, it's gonna fit.
It's all covered with vinegar.
Wait a minute. Let me guess.
Sui dumplings?
I think it's vinegared udon.
Vinegared udon?
Sukiyaki.
Sukiyaki? Sukiyaki?
What would go well with that?What's the fit?
If this were a guessing game, I'd be out.
Hey, hey, hey.
Eggs. That's it.
Eggs.
I don't even know if it's this deep in the pan.
That's the one you're taking.
Because the eggs are on the table.
It's messy.
Here, take it.
On the desk.
In front of the desk.
It's dirty.
He says, "Stupid, stupid, stupid.
What are you doing?
It's okay. It's okay.
Okay.
Good luck, Ume!
Let's go!
That's it!
Yum!
Good, good, good, good.
Yum, yum, yum, yum.
Surume.
Looks like it's covered.
I think I'm gonna wear this.
That's the only one that came to mind.
This one didn't come to mind.
Are you sure?
I don't know.I don't know.
Let's go.
Here we go.
Don.
Oh, yeah.
Yum.
Sushi rice
It's so good.
Sushi rice.
It's good with milk or something.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Yeah.
How can you serve sushi rice at that hour?
It's great.
It's really great.
Yes, sir.
Let's start around here, right?
If it's going to be covered...
Yes, I do.
Here you go, Don.
I don't care if it's creepy.
I like it.
It's okay.
I can see it in your eyes.
Bare pigs.
No, it's not.
I'll give you a hint... this is a wakame.As a hint, this is wakame seaweed
This is crab cakes
Here's a cucumber
Cute!
It's a little thing.
Oh, that's right.
It's a pig.
It's cute.
Cute, but...
No, no, no matter what you do to the creek, it's still prohibited to be cute
No, no, no, I want to be a creek.
No, no, no, I want to be a creek!
Let's go!
Dong!
Oh, wow.
Wow, it's good.
And the connection, too.
This is so good!
And the joints are kind of crunchy.
It looks so good.
So? Not seared?
It's good.
Here we go, genius.
Here we go.
Oh, my God.
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared.
Is this food?
How do you see it?
How do you see it from above?
Have you ever eaten one of these? Of course I have.Have you ever had one of these? Of course I have.
Yes, I have.
It's a snack.
It's a snack!
It's a salted fish.
Surume!
It's the President of Japan.
It's like torn up surume.
It's like it's stuck.
You've got a headache.
I got it.
Here you go, persimmon.
Open up!
Violet soup.
You have three bowls of violet soup.
But this one...
There's an egg.
Sukiyaki, right?
Sukiyaki, too.
So, Team Kaki...
Six points.
Only three?
I can't believe we're down like this.
This hurts!
What are you doing?
That's the dumbest mistake I've ever seen.
Can I go make violet juice?
I wonder if there are violets in it.
It's got Tsugure in it.
The title of the 33rd single
"Ohitorisama Tengoku" (One Man's Paradise).Decided to be a one-person heaven
Aichi Souvenirs will be on sale to the general public
29th start
The birth of the next shocking masterpiece
This is Michinose Mikku
This is Sakura Kawasaki
Subscribe to my channel!
Nice to meet you!
Bye bye!
Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much.